http://www.rfbe.com/privacy.html

RFBE.com Privacy Policy
At Relmax, Inc. we care about providing you with tools
and information to manage and protect your online privacy. We have developed
this privacy policy to inform you about what information this web site collects,
who may receive that information, what we may do with the information, and how
long we keep it. While we have made every attempt to make this policy as clear
as possible, if you have any further questions about it, please contact us:
Relmax, Inc.
Summary
For your convenience, the table below provides a summary our privacy policy.
Please consult the
rest of this document for more detailed information.
ActionReasonInformationCollectShareOpt OutEnterOpt OutShareCurrent activitySite administrationImprove the siteCustomizemultiple visitsCustomizethis visitGeneral habitsBuild your profileContact you
Traditional contact information
Internet contact information
Purchase information
System information
Navigation information
Identification information
Demographic and socio-economic information
Health information
Does this website use cookies to keep track of my information?
Yes, this website uses cookies.
What types of information does this website collect?
We collect the following types of information:
Traditional contact information such as mailing address, phone number, and fax number.
Internet contact information such email addresses.
Web pages visited, click stream data, and other navigation information.
Non-financial identification information, such as username and password combinations.
User content such as forum messages and instant messages.
Why is this website collecting the information?
We collect the information for the following purposes:
To complete the current activity of the visitor.
For website administration purposes.
To evaluate, review, or improve the website.
To customize the website for the user on multiple visits to the site.
To notify visitors of updates to the sites, and/or contact them to market products or services.
Who will receive the information?
The information will be shared with the following parties:
Our internal staff.
Can I review my information?
Our website allows you to review all the information we keep about you.
What if I think there are inaccuracies in my information?
If you believe we are not handling your information in accordance with our privacy policy, please contact our customer service department.
Contact information is available at http://www.rfbe.com/contact.html.
If for some reason we have violated our privacy policy, we will correct the error as soon as you notify us.
